Guide to the Avram Finkelstein Papers, 1968-2015 (bulk 1986-2014) MSS.422
Fales Library and Special Collections
Avram Finkelstein Papers
1968-2015
1986-2014
Fales Library and Special Collections
Finkelstein, Avram
MSS.422
12 Linear Feet (10 boxes)
The Avram Finkelstein Papers consist of materials related to the life and work of New York artist and gay rights activist Avram Finkelstein. The bulk of the collection focuses on AIDS-related groups, organizations, individuals, and art collectives responding to political and social movements between the mid-1980s and the late 1990s. A fair amount of material is also drawn from Finkelstein's affiliations with ACT UP, his affinity group Anonymous Queers, and the art collective Gran Fury.
Biographical note
Avram Finkelstein is an artist and writer living in Brooklyn. He is a founding member of the art collective, Gran Fury, with whom he collaborated on public art projects for international institutions including The Whitney Museum of American Art, The Venice Biennale, ArtForum, MOCA LA, The New Museum of Contemporary Art, Creative Time, and The Public Art Fund. The collective had its first retrospective at 80 WSE in 2012, and has work in the permanent collections of The Whitney, MoMA, The New Museum and The New York Public Library.
His solo work has shown at The Whitney Museum, The Cooper Hewitt Museum, Exit Art, La MaMa La Galleria and The Leslie Lohman Museum, and is in the permanent collections of MoMA, The Whitney, The Metropolitan Museum, The New Museum, The Smithsonian, The Brooklyn Museum
His recent workshops and lectures focus on the "Flash Collective," a new paradigm for rethinking the public sphere, an experiment in political art-making focused on the creation of a one day collective to produce a single art intervention in a public space.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of materials used and produced by individuals, groups and organizations in response to the AIDS epidemic. Avram's Papers not only contain a number of historical documents, but also help showcase the range of public and private responses issued from different collectives involved with AIDS activism in the late 1980s and beyond. Especially well-represented groups and projects include: ACT UP, Anonymous Queers, Gran Fury and Silence=Death. Ephemera in the collection includes but is not limited to redacted government documents, broadsheets, notes for artworks and articles, t-shirts, and posters.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title, which generally indicates the group or person associated with the folder contents. Within those groupings, materials are organized chronologically, where the date is known.
Related Materials
Bill Bytsura ACT UP Photography Collection (MSS.313)
Alan Klein Papers (MSS.118)
Jay Blotcher Papers (MSS.137)
Michelangelo Signorile Papers (MSS.131)
Lee Snider Photograph Collection (MSS.248)
Provenance
The Avram Finkelstein Papers were acquired by NYU's Fales Library & Special Collections from Avram Finkelstein in December 2014. The collection had been stored in Finkelstein's apartment in Brooklyn previous to transfer to NYU.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
AIDS (Disease) and art -- United States.; Activists -- United States -- 1980-2011.; Artistic collaboration; Political activists.; Politics in art.; Artists |z New York (State) |z New York |x Political activity.; Rafsky, Bob; Gran Fury (Artists' collective); ACT UP New York (Organization); Klein, Alan; ACT UP (Organization); Anonymous Queers; Silence = Death Project; Guerrilla Girls (Group of artists); Fierce Pussy (Artists' group)
- Series I, 1987-2014
  - 3: [affinity group] ephemera, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ACT UP: fact sheets and flyers, March 1987-June 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ACT UP: sign-in sheets, June 22-29, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACT UP: "Let the Record Show...", November 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACT UP: press, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACT UP: organizing material [1 of 2], 1987-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACT UP: organizing material [2 of 2], 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ACT UP FBI Files: Know Your Rights broadsheet, c. 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ACT UP FBI Files [1 of 4], 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ACT UP FBI Files [2 of 4], 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACT UP FBI Files [3 of 4], 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACT UP FBI Files [4 of 4], 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ACT UP: teach-in about queer history: "A His & Herstory of Queer Activism", June 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ACT UP: "A Critique of the AIDS Clinical Trials Group", March 1, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ACT UP: show announcements, incl. first ACT UP fundraiser, 1990, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ACT UP: letters and responses to moratorium of clinical trials, February, March 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ACT UP: "A Direct Action Political Model of Community Research for AIDS Prevention" by Maxine Wolfe, February 21, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ACT UP at the Republican Convention, August 17-27, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ACT UP: outreach contacts, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ACT UP affinity group project: AIDS Profiteer stickers, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Scope and Content
    Members of this ACT UP affinity group went into drug stores and placed these stickers on prescription bottles produced by targeted pharmaceutical companies.
  - ACT UP Congressional Action Working Group [1 of 2], 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ACT UP Congressional Action Working Group [2 of 2], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ACT UP media committee: AIDS buzzwords handout, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ACT UP Seattle: stickers and pin, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ACT UP Women's Action Committee: "Doctors, Liars and Thieves" film transcript, July 22, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Against Equality with Ryan Conrad: Ephemera, 2011, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Anonymous Queers source material for first broadsheet, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Anonymous Queers: notes and responses for the broadsheet newsletters [1 of 3], 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Anonymous Queers: notes and responses for the broadsheet newsletters [2 of 3], 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Anonymous Queers: notes and responses for the broadsheet newsletters [3 of 3], 1989-[1990] (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Anonymous Queers source material, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Anonymous Queers: David Robinson letter re: broadsheet "I Hate Straights", July 2, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Anonymous Queers first broadsheet, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Anonymous Queers (and subgroup) ephemera, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Anonymous Queers: second project, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Anonymous Queers second broadsheet ephemera, June 1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Anonymous Queers: Stonewall 25th anniversary broadsheet, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Arts Working Group t-shirt at Occupy Wall Street: "Art Killed My Dreams", c. 2011 (Box 8)
  - Avram: Daily News coverage of first protest, March 25, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Avram: "Enjoy AZT" notes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Avram: "Enjoy AZT" t-shirt, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Avram: fax zap to Steven Joseph's office, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Avram: Names Project Quilt unfolding ceremony, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Avram: "Let the Record Show..." notes, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Avram: "New York Crimes" source material, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Avram's photos/postcard of Jeffrey Pittu + Public Art Fund's "Messages to the Public", January 1, 1989-January 15, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Avram: catalogs, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Avram: catalogs, 1990-2014 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Avram: notes for NIH Day of Desperation, January 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Avram: Marvel Super-heroes Summer Special X-Men Issue, Summer 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Avram: "A Thumbnail Sketch of the History of Scientific Research in America" for the McClintock Project, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Avram: "News Story on ACT UP/FBI", 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Avram: exhibition and permissions correspondence, 2010-2014 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Avram: Exhibition catalogs, 2010-2014 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Avram: Flash Collective ephemera, March 2014 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Avram: Diane Neumaier slides documenting subway graffiti, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Avram: drafts and notes for articles [1 of 6], c. 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Avram: drafts and notes for articles [2 of 6], c. 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Avram: drafts and notes for articles [3 of 6], c. 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Avram: drafts and notes for articles [4 of 6], c. 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Avram: drafts and notes for articles [5 of 6], c. 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Avram: drafts and notes for articles [6 of 6], c. 1989-1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Avram: early press clippings, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Avram: press, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Avram's journal pages documenting Silence=Death, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Avram's journal, January 1984-June 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Avram bought this journal in Japan in 1983, but began writing in it early 1984. Kept by his bed, the journal includes dream entries, notes for projects, and notes from meetings from the first years of ACT UP. The first bookmark opens to an entry that sketches the first Silence=Death project. The second bookmark opens to an entry in which Bill Olander offers Avram the windows of the New Museum for Gran Fury's "Let the Record Show..." exhibition (1987-1988).
  - Avram source material: AIDS advertisements and ephemera, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Avram collaboration with Don Moffett: "Fact or Fiction?" and source material, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Avram collaboration with Don Moffett: rejected cover ideas for "Reports from the Holocaust", c. 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Avram featured in still from Vincent Gagliostro's video footage, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: ACT UP campaign notes, c. 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: "Storm the NIH" and other, May 1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: Day of Desperation action ephemera and notes, January 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: "Enjoy AZT" rationale for Cooper Hewitt Show, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Avram collaboration with Visual AIDS, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [1 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [2 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [3 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [4 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [5 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [6 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [7 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [8 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS [9 of 9], 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Bob Rafsky material, November 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Canadian groups: ephemera, 2009, 2012, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CDC Action Planning Group: notes and documents, c. 1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - CDC Working Committee: "Background on the Centers for Disease Control", c. 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Civil Disobedience: President Quayle flyer, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - COSTAS affinity group: photos and "A Costa Her/History", March 2, 1991, June 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Dyke Action Machine: "DAM! Incorporated", 2008 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gran Fury: "Men Use Condoms or Beat It" sticker, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Gran Fury: notes, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gran Fury: Wall Street money, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gran Fury ad in the Bessie's Award program: "During This Program at Least 6 People with AIDS Will Die", 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gran Fury poster: "You've Got Blood On Your Hands, Ed Koch", 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Gran Fury postcards, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Scope and Contents
    These postcards were mostly produced by ACT UP. Included in this folder is a photograph Avram took of the "Kissing Doesn't Kill" bus campaign that shows white-out graffiti done by lesbian activists in San Francisco.
  - Gran Fury t-shirt: "The Government Has Blood on Its Hands", c. 1988-1989 (Box 8)
    This t-shirt was produced by ACT UP for an FDA Action.
  - Gran Fury: press and permissions, 1988-2010 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Gran Fury: "Kissing Doesn't Kill" notes and "Art Against AIDS" poster template, March 17, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Gran Fury catalogs [1 of 2], 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gran Fury catalogs [2 0f 2], 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gran Fury ephemera, 1989-1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gran Fury: Avram's editing notes for "Kissing Doesn't Kill", [March 1990] (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Gran Fury: Venice Biennale, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Gran Fury: "Good Luck" notes from the Decades Show, c. 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Gran Fury collaboration with Prostitutes of New York (PONY): "Love For Sale...Free Condoms Inside" at the New Museum, February 16-April 7, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gran Fury: unseen third project "The Christian Agenda Revealed", 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Gran Fury: "Read My Lips" ephemera, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Gran Fury t-shirt: "Read My Lips", c. 1995 (Box 8)
  - Gran Fury: Harvard Art Museum "ACT UP New York" show catalog, April 2010 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Gran Fury: 80 WSE show front piece, 2011 (Box 8)
  - Gran Fury: 80 WSE show material, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Gran Fury catalogue raisonne for 80 WSE show, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Gran Fury: notes and interview for 80 WSE show, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Gran Fury's Opening Ceremony reissued t-shirt: "4 questions", 2012 (Box 8)
  - Gran Fury: original roll of stickers produced by ACT UP "The Government Has Blood on Its Hands", undated (Box 8)
  - Harper Canada AIDS action ephemera, C. 2012 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - The Lesbian Avengers 1994 calendar (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - The Marys: political funeral flyer, c. 1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Pink Tank: "We Will Not Protect You", 2004 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Queer Action Figures: zine, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Queer Nation: "The Queer National," vol. 1, no.2, June 1991 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Queer Nation collaboration with Joe Ferrari: "Smash Heterosexism", undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Queer Nation t-shirt: "Queers Bash Back", undated (Box 8)
  - Silence=Death: AIDSGATE t-shirt, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Silence=Death: AIDSGATE transparency, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Silence=Death blank postcard, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Silence=Death early handout for Foley Square, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Silence=Death: press, permissions and catalogs [1 of 2], 1987-1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Silence=Death: press, permissions and catalogs [2 of 2], 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Silence=Death AIDS monument at Sheridan Square: photos and letters, c. 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Silence=Death Ortez Alderson commemorative pin, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Silence=Death: William O. Johnston, Jr. obituary and memorial piece, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Silence=Death correspondence and annotated folder re: printing, 1991, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Silence=Death pins, stickers and magnet, produced by ACT UP, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Silence=Death t-shirt, undated (Box 8)
  - Treatment Action Group (TAG) research, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Treatment of Data Committee research [1 of 2], 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Treatment of Data Committee research [2 of 2], 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Treatment of Data Committee: FDA Action Handbook, September 21, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights: "Civil Rights Aspects of Public Health Policies and Initiatives to Control AIDS", 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - various collective ephemera: ACT UP, Adam Ralston, AIDS Policy Project, Art + Positive, Boy with Arms Akimbo, CDC working committee [1 of 2], 1988-1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - various collective ephemera: Fierce Pussy, GANG, Little Elvis, Nelson Santos, Q-Think, Tom Kalem, WHAM! [2 of 2], 1988-2013, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - various collectives and other individuals: ephemera, 1990-2014, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Visual AIDS tote: AIDS On Going Going On, 2013 (Box 8)
  - Wave 3 t-shirt: "Harmony Moore has to die", undated (Box 8)
  - XXX Fruit literary arts quarterly introduction, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Series I: Oversize, 1968-2014
  - ACT UP: "What does Koch plan to do about AIDS? Invest in marble and granite" poster, March 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - ACT UP Reports, no. 2, 4, and 5, June, September/October 1989, 1991/1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - ACT UP oversize posters, 1990, undated (Folder 12 Left)
    "We Think He's Going to Hell Too," 1990 "If you fuck without a condom you risk HIV infection and can get AIDS," n.d.
  - ACT UP: funeral action, c. 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ACT UP demonstration sign: "Which One Do You Trust? Condoms Prevent AIDS Cardinals Don't", undated (Folder 1 Left)
  - ACT UP Seattle oversize poster, undated (Folder 11 Left)
    for the Health and Human Services Action in D.C., featuring David Wojnarowicz quote.
  - ACT UP: "Stop this Monster!" poster, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Demographics AIDS flag, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Anonymous Queers: various broadsides and newsletters, 1992, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Avram: first activist art "sheep who die silently are no use as victims", 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Avram: first screenprint: "Nous Sommes Tous Indesirables", 1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Avram: "New York Crimes" mock-up, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Avram: "New York Crimes" source material, c. 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Avram: mock-ups for "Enjoy AZT" and "Serial Killer", 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Avram: XXX Fruit match print, December 1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Avram: "Lifelines: Recent Work by Avram Finkelstein" at the Harbor Gallery, February 15-March 14, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Avram: leather jacket panel featuring the bloody handprint, undated (Box 11)
  - Avram collaboration with the AIDS Policy Project: posters, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Avram collaboration with Don Moffett: Ed Koch poster mock-ups and source material, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Avram collaboration with Don Moffett: rejected cover idea for Larry Kramer's Reports from the Holocaust, c. 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Avram collaboration with Don Moffett: "WACK-O: Extreme Politics and the Poster" at St. Lawrence University, January 26-February 18, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: POS Magazine source material and mock-ups, c. 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: Enjoy AZT poster, c. 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: Storm the N.I.H. ACT UP poster, May 21, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: "Serial Killer" (for Storm the N.I.H. Action), May 21, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Avram collaboration with Vincent Gagliostro: material for the George Bush Action, February 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - CDC demonstration signs, undated (Folder 14 Right)
    "The CDC is a Dead End" "Undercounting AIDS Cases Kills"
  - CISPES appropriated New York Times, January 5, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Don Moffett: Ronald Reagan "History Will Plague Him" poster, c. 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Dyke Action Machine oversize poster, undated (Folder 10 Left)
  - Fierce Pussy: Poster for Visual AIDS, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Global Justice: Annual Pride Art Exhibition poster, June 16-September 25, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Gran Fury: "Art is Not Enough" at the Kitchen, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Gran Fury mock-ups, c. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Gran Fury: Nine Days of Fury, Spring 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Gran Fury oversize posters, 1988, 1993 (Folder 15 Right)
    produced by ACT UP. "AIDS: 1 in 61," 1988 "4 Questions," 1993
  - Gran Fury: Read My Lips Proof, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Gran Fury: 7 Days article: "A Biennial of Our Own: What You Won't See at the Whitney", May 3, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Gran Fury: "New York Crimes", 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Gran Fury: oversize poster for "The Decade Show: Frameworks of Identity in the 1980s", May 11-August 19, 1990 (Folder 9 Left)
  - Gran Fury: The Christian Agenda Revealed, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Gran Fury: Alternative Histories @ Exit Art promotional poster, September 24-November 24, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Gran Fury: 80 WSE show material, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Gran Fury: Printouts from ACT UP demonstrations for 80 WSE Show, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - The Kitchen: promotional poster for "Video for Advocacy & Self-Empowerment", April 6-April 8, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Lee Shy: Re-imagining of a Queer Family, c. 1993 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Lesbian Avengers: ephemera, 1993, 1994, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Michael O'Brien for ACT UP: "If You Fuck Without A Condom...", c. 1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Ohio State University: AIDS: The Artists' Response exhibition catalog, February 24-April 16, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Poster Virus: AIDS Action Now posters, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - QUASH publication: "Why I Hated the March on Washington", c. 1993 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Queer Nation: Calvin Klein poster, c. 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Russian group oversize posters, 1990 (Folder 8 Left)
  - Silence=Death poster, produced by ACT UP, 1987 (Folder 38)
  - Silence=Death poster proof and instructions for the printer, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Tom Kalem: 1968/1988 stickers (Box 10, Folder 19)